<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Logic Games</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="games">Games</string>
    <string name="aboutText">Logic game is a collection of 2D logical puzzles, just like the famous minesweeper. \n\n Available for free on Android\n\n(C) Bence Konecsni, v1.0</string>

    <string name="parks_description">Plant the tree, but not too close to each other!</string>
    <string name="minesweeper_description">The good old minesweeper</string>
    <string name="lighten_up_description">Lighten your whole room!</string>
    <string name="sumscrapers_description">Find the skyline!</string>
    <string name="skyscrapers_description">Sum the skyline!</string>

    <string name="parks_summary">Plant one tree in each Park, row and column.</string>
    <string name="minesweeper_summary">I know you are familiar with this one :)</string>
    <string name="lighten_up_summary">Place lightbulbs to light up all the room squares.</string>
    <string name="sumscrapers_summary">Guess the sum of the skyscrapers from the skyline.</string>
    <string name="skyscrapers_summary">Guess skyscrapers from the skyline.</string>

    <string name="parks_rules">You have a few differently coloured areas, called Parks on the board.\n The goal is to plant trees, following the given rules:\n\n
        1. A tree can not touch another tree, not even diagonally.\n
        2. Each Park must have exactly one tree.\n
        3. There must be exactly one tree in each row and column as well.</string>
    <string name="minesweeper_rules">Find the mines on the field.\nNumbers tell you how many mines there are close by, touching that number horizontally, vertically or diagonally.</string>
    <string name="lighten_up_rules">What you see from above is a room and the marked squares are walls.\n
        The goal is to put lightbulbs in the room so that all the blank (non-wall) squares are lit, following these rules:\n\n
        1. Lighbulbs light all free, unblocked squares horizontally and vertically.\n
        2. A lightbulb can not light another lightbulb.\n
        3. Walls block light. Also walls with a number tell you how many lightbulbs are adjacent to i, horizontally and vertically.\n
        4. Walls without a number can have any number of lightbulbs. However, lightbulbs do not need to be adjacent to a wall.\n</string>
    <string name="sumscrapers_rules">Please play \'Skyscrapers\' first, as this is a variaton of that game.\n
        All the rules about \'Skyscrapers\' are valid, but the numbers you see on the borders tell you the SUM of the heights of the Skyscrapers you see.</string>
    <string name="skyscrapers_rules">The central grid represents a city, as seen from above. Each square contains a Skyscraper with different height.\n
        The goal is to guess the height of each Skyscraper.\n Skysrapers height ranges from 1 to the size of the city (number or rows/columns).\n
        Each row and column can not have two Skyscrapers with same height. \n Outside the city, on the borders, the numbers indicate the \'Skyline\'.\n
        The Skyline tells you how many Skyscrapers you can see from there, keeping in mind that a higher Skyscraper hides a lower one.</string>
</resources>
